const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Put these sentences in indirect speech"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:'"Did you sleep well last night, Granny?" she asked.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked Granny if she had slept well the previous night.",2:"She asked Granny if she was sleeping well the previous night.",3:"She asked Granny if she slept well the previous night."}},{type:"test",question:'"Did you enjoy the show last night?" he said.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked if I had enjoyed the show the previous night.",2:"He asked if I enjoyed the show the previous night.",3:"He asked if had I enjoyed the show the previous night."}},{type:"test",question:'"Did you get everything, Ann?" he asked again.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked Ann again if she had got everything.",2:"He asked Ann again what she got.",3:"He asked Ann again had she got everything."}},{type:"test",question:'"Does your watch tell you what year it is?" said the man.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The man asked if my watch told what year it was.",2:"The man asked what my watch told.",3:"The man asked if my watch had told what year it was."}},{type:"test",question:'"Does he know French and English?" said Peter.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Peter asked if he knew French and English.",2:"Peter asked if he had known French and English.",3:"Peter asked did he know French and English."}},{type:"test",question:'"Do you always have supper at seven, Granny?" she asked.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked Granny if she always had supper at seven.",2:"She asked Granny if she always had had supper at seven.",3:"She asked Granny if she always has supper at seven."}},{type:"test",question:'"Is it a story about me?" he said.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked if it was a story about him.",2:"He asked if it is a story about him.",3:"He asked if it would be a story about him."}},{type:"test",question:'"Are you ready to start?" the teacher said.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"The teacher asked us if we were ready to start.",2:"The teacher asked us if we had been ready to start.",3:"The teacher asked us if we are ready to start."}},{type:"test",question:'"Are we having tea in the kitchen?" she asked Tom.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked Tom if they were having tea in the kitchen.",2:"She asked Tom why they were having tea in the kitchen.",3:"She asked Tom if they had tea in the kitchen."}},{type:"test",question:'"Will you marry me, Vanya?" she said.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked Vanya if he would marry her.",2:"She asked Vanya would he marry her.",3:"She asked Vanya if he married her."}},{type:"test",question:'He said, "Will you take your exams in January?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked if I would take my exams in January.",2:"He asked if I will take my exams in January.",3:"He asked if I took my exams in January."}},{type:"test",question:'She said, "Will he make a good husband?"',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked if he would make a good husband.",2:"She asked if he will make a good husband.",3:"She asked if will he make a good husband."}},{type:"test",question:'"Will I see you again?" he said.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked if he would see me again.",2:"He asked if he will see me again.",3:"He asked if he sees me again."}},{type:"test",question:'"Do you like coffee with sugar in it?" he asked.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"He asked if I liked coffee with sugar in it.",2:"He asked if I like coffee with sugar in it.",3:"He asked do I like coffee with sugar in it."}},{type:"test",question:'"Damira, do you like football or not?" she asked.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"She asked Damira if she liked football or not.",2:"She asked Damira does she like football or doesn't.",3:"She asked Damira if did she like football or not."}}]}]};export{e as default};
